sallyhansen.com 2011-04-22

# Privacy Policy | Coty.com

  | 

### Privacy Policy 

**_Coty's Online Privacy Policy - General_**  
Coty respects your privacy. We take precautions to safeguard your personally identifiable information. At the same time, Coty collects information that you voluntarily provide to us online as part of our continuing efforts to improve our product offerings and enhance your online visits to our various brand websites, including, Rimmel London, Stetson Cologne, Stetson Untamed, Preferred Stock, Jovan Sexy, Jovan White Musk, Jovan Heat, Jennifer Lopez Fragrances, Vanilla Musk, Calgon Take Me Away, Celine Dion Beauty, Exclamation by Coty, Aspen Cologne, Vanilla Fields, the Healing Garden, Cotyshop, and Coty Wild. We encourage you to read about Coty's privacy policy and practices concerning online data use. 

**_Coty's Privacy Policies_  
** Coty offers its line of fragrance and beauty care products in many countries. Individual countries often have different privacy laws. In addition to our general online privacy policy, Coty has adopted the following supplemental country-specific policies.

**Coty's Online Privacy Policy - General  
** ** _Privacy Notice_**  
Coty knows you care how personal information about you is used by us and/or shared with others. Coty values your trust. We seek to safeguard your personally identifiable information and honor your requests for privacy. This notice describes our online privacy policy and practices, including what information we collect and how we use it.  
By visiting any of our various brand sites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. Unless you tell us otherwise, whenever you submit personally identifiable information to us online, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, as described herein.  
Coty collects data from our various brand websites (i.e., Rimmel London, Stetson Cologne, Stetson Untamed, Preferred Stock, Jovan Sexy, Jovan White Musk, Jovan Heat, Jennifer Lopez Fragrances, Vanilla Musk, Calgon Take Me Away, Celine Dion Beauty, Exclamation by Coty, Aspen Cologne, Vanilla Fields, the Healing Garden, Cotyshop, and Coty Wild) through sampling offers, sweepstakes entries, newsletters, etc. We collect information concerning your lifestyle/interests, preferences and attitudes to assist us in our product development and marketing. We are also interested in making your visits to our websites useful and enjoyable. We try to customize your website experience in a way that is tailored to your unique interests. At the same time, we give you options to assist us in customizing your visits. This is accomplished through our [_Beauty Pass_](http://sampollnet.coty.com/ScentStrip) link. 

**_Beauty Pass_**  
Through Beauty Pass at [_www.cotyshop.com_](http://www.cotyshop.com/), you can request free samples of Coty products, find out more about sweepstakes, new products and product promotions. Beauty Pass also allows you to customize and manage your Coty profile. If you are a registered user of Beauty Pass, you can access a global opt in/opt out level for all of our brand websites, complete with your personal information. For brands that have quizzes or contests, visitors are eligible to modify their information during the period the contest or quiz is live. We want you to have fun while knowing that your personally identifiable information is protected. 

**_What Personal Information Does Coty Gather?_**  
The information Coty learns from customers helps us continually improve the services we provide to you. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **_Information You Give Us_** : Coty receives and stores any information you enter on our Web sites or give us in any other way. However, you can choose not to provide certain information. However, if you do so, then you might not be able to take full advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future visits based on your interests, awarding prizes for sweepstakes/contests, improving our service and communicating more effectively with you.
  * **_Automatic Information_** : Coty receives and stores certain types of information automatically whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use 'cookies.' In that way, we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our site. There are a number of companies that offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although Coty will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, you should be aware that these disabling tools exist. 

**_What Are Cookies?_**

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that Coty transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They enable our systems to recognize your browser. If we recognize you, Coty can provide more customized or personalized features each time you log on to one of our brand websites.
  * The 'help' portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and/or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our sites' features. Coty recommends that you leave them turned on.
  * It is possible that some of Coty's business partners may also use cookies on our websites. However, Coty has no access to, or control over, these cookies. Therefore, we do not accept any responsibility for such use. 

**_What About Pixel Tags?_**  
When you visit Coty's websites or view one of our e-mails, we may use pixel tags (also called 'clear gifs'), tracking links and/or similar technology to note some of the pages you visit on our websites. These help us personalize your experience. We may also use pixel tags to determine what types of e-mail your browser supports. Coty may use the information collected through pixel tags, tracking links and similar technology in combination with your personally identifiable information. 

**_Safeguards Concerning The Use Of Your Personal Information_**

  * Coty does _not_ read your private online communications.  

  * Coty does _not_ use any information about where you personally go on the Web and we do not give it out to others.  

  * Coty does _not_ give out your personally identifiable information such as telephone number, credit card information or screen names. Coty also gives you the opportunity to correct your personal contact and other personally identifiable information that you have provided to us at any time.  

  * Coty may use information about the kinds of products you buy to make other marketing offers to you, unless you tell us not to by opting-out via email or through your Beauty Pass registration.

Coty, via your 

[_Beauty Pass_](http://sampollnet.coty.com/ScentStrip) registration, gives you choices about how your personal information is used.  

  * The information you provide may be used by Coty to create and deliver to you newsletters, e-mails, surveys or other communications containing product information, offers, sweepstakes, contest information, promotions or information concerning your order.  

  * Coty may use the information you provide in an aggregate form for internal business and planning purposes, such as generating demographic data and statistics or developing marketing plans.  

  * Coty may collect, store and accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of our websites, such as information regarding which of our pages, brand sites, contests or promotions are most popular. Coty may share or transfer such non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees or partners.

Coty may disclose information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Coty, as a rule, does not itself conduct direct sales of our products online; however, in the event of any on-line purchases, Coty may exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations to process or fulfill orders submitted by you and for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

  * Coty may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our websites, track traffic patterns and gather demographic information for aggregate use. 

**_Do We Share the Information We Receive?_**  
Information about our customers is an important part of Coty's business. However, Coty is _not_ in the business of selling our database to others. We share customer information only with subsidiaries we control, affiliates or specific business partners or agents and only as described below. 

  * **_Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control_** : Coty works closely with other business partners including our licensors such as adidas and our Sony/Epic affiliation. In some cases, these businesses operate stores or separate websites linked to our websites or will want to send offerings to you, but only when you tell us/them to by opting to receive partner information. You can tell when another business/partner is involved in a promotion and we only share customer information with that business when you tell us by opting-in.
  * **_Agents_** : Coty employs other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. However, they are not authorized by Coty to use it for other purposes or provide it to anyone else.
  * **_Protection of Coty and Others_** : Coty reserves its right to release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves, our users or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * **_Links_** : Coty's websites may contain links to and from other websites. Please be aware that we are _not_ responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This privacy policy only applies to the information Coty collects on our various brand websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any other websites to which you link from our websites.
  * **_Third Parties_** : Coty may retain other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include data analyses firms, customer support specialists, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings, sweepstakes, contests or promotions) and web-hosting companies. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions. However, they are not authorized by Coty to use such information for any other purpose or transfer it to anyone else. 

**_Choice - Opt Out_**  
If you receive any future e-mailings from Coty, you may opt out of these mailings at any time by clicking on a link in the e-mail you receive. Our e-mail practices are designed to comply with the United States Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (the 'CAN-SPAM Act'). 

**_Children_**  
Our websites are directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. Coty will not approve applications of, or establish or maintain accounts or memberships for, any child whom Coty knows to be under the age of 13. Coty does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Coty's various brand websites are designed to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. In that regard, we seek parental permission before collecting personal information from anyone under the age of fourteen.

**_Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions  
_** If you choose to visit Coty's brand sites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of the laws of the State of New York in the USA. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also. The use of information that Coty gathers is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. Coty may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes that have been posted. 

**_Secure Communications  
_** All pages where you provide personal credit card information use Secure Server Software (SSL) encryption technology. SSL is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure transactions. Coty uses secure technology, privacy protection controls and restrictions on employee access in order to safeguard your personal information. 

**_Online Privacy Policy ' Compliance_**  
Coty supports industry self-regulatory efforts. We believe such actions are the best way to protect the privacy of the consumer. Currently, Coty is actively seeking participation in a number of standard-setting groups focused on information practices and individual privacy issues. 

Back to Top

**Terms and Conditions of Use**  
Welcome to Coty's web sites. COTY AND OUR AFFILIATES PROVIDE OUR SERVICES TO YOU SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING CONDITIONS. IF YOU VISIT AND USE ANY OF OUR WEB SITES, YOU ACCEPT THESE CONDITIONS. PLEASE READ THEM CAREFULLY. In addition, when you use any current or future service or visit the web site of any business affiliated with us, whether or not included in this web site, you also will be subject to the guidelines and conditions applicable to such other service(s) or business(es) or web site(s), including any applicable privacy policies thereof which may differ from Coty's policies. 

**_COPYRIGHT_**  
All content included on this site, including but not limited to, text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations and software, is the property of Coty or its content suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of Coty or its software suppliers and is protected by United States and international copyright laws. 

**_TRADEMARKS_**  
Marks indicated on our site are registered trademarks of Coty or its affiliates, including licensors, in the United States and other countries. All other trademarks not owned by Coty or its subsidiaries that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by Coty or its subsidiaries. 

**_LIMITED LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS_**  
Coty grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify this site, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of Coty. This license does not include: any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without the express written consent of Coty. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) without Coty's express written consent. You may not use any meta tags or any other 'hidden text' utilizing our name or trademarks without the express written consent of Coty. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by Coty. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of Coty so long as the link does not portray Coty, its affiliates, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, offensive or any other manner which Coty in its sole discretion, may find to be objectionable. You may not use any Coty logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without Coty's express written permission. 

**_REVIEWS, COMMENTS, COMMUNICATIONS, AND OTHER CONTENT  
_** Visitors may post reviews, comments, and other content, send e-cards and other communications, and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of 'Spam.' You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a card or other content. Coty reserves the right (but does not have the obligation) to remove or edit such content in its sole discretion.  
If you do post content or submit material, you grant Coty and its affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant Coty and its affiliates and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if we or they so choose. You represent and warrant: that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify Coty and its affiliates, including licensors against all claims, including an attorneys' fees relating to that defense thereof, resulting from content you supply. Coty has the right but not the obligation, to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content in its sole discretion. Coty.com takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party. 

**_COPYRIGHT COMPLAINTS  
_** Coty and its affiliates respect the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with detailed information concerning your claim.

**_PRODUCT DESCRIPTIONS  
_** Coty and its affiliates attempt to be accurate at all times. However, Coty does not warrant that descriptions or other content of this site are accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. 

**_OTHER BUSINESSES  
_** Parties other than Coty and our subsidiaries operate stores, provide services or sell product lines on this site. For example, other businesses and individuals offer products. In addition, Coty provides links to the sites of affiliated companies and certain other businesses. Coty is not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals or the content of their Web sites. Coty does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, and/or content of any of these web sites or the web sites of any other third parties. You should carefully review each web site's privacy policy statements and other conditions of use. 

**_DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY  
_** THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY COTY ON AN 'AS IS' AND 'AS AVAILABLE' BASIS. COTY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THIS SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, COTY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. COTY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS SITE, ITS SERVERS, OR E-MAIL SENT FROM COTY ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. COTY WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.  
 **APPLICABLE LAW**  
By visiting this web site, you agree that the laws of the State of New York, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms and Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Coty or its affiliates. 

**_SITE POLICIES, MODIFICATION, AND SEVERABILITY  
_** Please review our other policies, posted on this site. These policies also govern your visit to Coty's other web sites. We reserve the right to make changes to our site, policies, and these Terms and Conditions of Use at any time. If any of these terms and conditions shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that term or condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining terms and condition. 

Back to Top

**Coty's US Privacy Policy**  
Coty respects the privacy of every individual about whom we have information. Coty pledges to conduct its business according to these principles: 

**Notice, Access and Choice** 'Coty recognizes that individuals should be informed about how personal information about them is used. They should also have choices about the dissemination of that information. To understand what information Coty compiles, how it is used and to learn how to exercise choice or access zuch information, please read the information on Notice, Access and Choice. 

**Compliance** 'Currently, Coty is actively seeking participation in a number of standard-setting groups focused on information practices and individual privacy issues. To learn more about Coty's compliance initiatives, please read our section on Compliance. 

**Accuracy** 'Coty maintains quality-control procedures. These are aimed at ensuring that the information we compile and process is accurate and complete. We will respond promptly to any questions about the accuracy of information from clients and consumers. 

**Security** 'Coty maintains security procedures aimed at preventing unauthorized access to personal information. We use multi-level security systems to control access to our sensitive information. All users must have the appropriate password-protected access codes and be expressly authorized to access certain data and applications. Coty conducts audits from time to time on our internal and external information systems to help preserve the integrity of customer data. We also maintain physical security for our facilities and limit access to certain critical areas of the business. 

**Online Practice** s'Coty's online privacy practices apply to the collection and use of information collected online from individuals, prospects and customers who visit our various brand websites. Our Online Privacy Policy describes Coty's use of cookies and what choices individuals have pertaining to the use of information collected by such technologies. More information can be found in Coty's Online Policy - General. 

**_US Privacy Policy ' Notice, Access, Choice_**  
 ** _Notice, Access and Choice_**  
Coty recognizes that individuals should be informed as to how personal information about them is used and has choices pertaining to the use and dissemination of that information. Notices should be provided that explain the collection, use and distribution of personally identifiable information. Most importantly, individuals should have the choice to opt out of the use of their data in marketing campaigns if they so desire. Similarly, Coty believes individuals should have access to personal information a company has about them that will be used for commercial reference purposes. Coty conforms to self-regulatory guidelines for providing an individual with notice, access and choice.  
Consumers may request an Opt-out by sending an email to [_talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) or by sending a letter to E-business Consumer Contact, Coty Beauty, One Park Avenue 5th Floor, NY, NY 10016 An individual may have access to his or her individual information in the Beauty Pass area at [_www.cotyshop.com_](http://www.cotyshop.com/) or by sending an email to [_talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) . If an individual wants to change or correct inaccurate information or have that information removed, he or she should contact us at [_talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) . 

**_US Privacy Policy ' Compliance_**  
Coty supports consumer privacy.  
Coty supports industry self-regulatory efforts. Coty believes such actions are an effective way to protect the privacy of the consumer. Coty monitors state and federal laws to ensure compliance with any regulatory requirements.  
Currently, Coty is actively seeking participation in a number of standard-setting groups focused on information practices and individual privacy issues. 

Back to Top

**UK Privacy Policy**  
Coty respects the privacy of every individual in the UK about whom it holds personal information. Coty pledges to conduct its business according to the following principles. 

**Notice, Access and Choice** 'Coty recognizes that consumers have rights regarding the use and dissemination of information about themselves. Notices should be provided that explain the collection, use and distribution of personally identifiable information. Coty conforms to legal and self-regulatory guidelines for providing a consumer notice, access and choice. To understand what information Coty compiles, how it is used and to learn how to exercise choice and access, please read the information on Notice, Access and Choice. 

**Compliance** 'Coty is registered with the Information Commissioner and has implemented internal controls and procedures designed to comply with the Data Protection Act of 1998. Coty is currently working with recognized organizations that support consumer privacy in an effort to maintain and develop appropriate industry guidelines and regulations to safeguard the consumer's rights to privacy. Coty supports industry self-regulation and believes such actions are the best way to protect privacy. Coty will register with the U.S. Department of Commerce under the EU Safe Harbor program. More information can be found under Coty's EU Safe Harbor Policy. 

**Accuracy** 'Coty maintains quality-control procedures aimed at ensuring our information is accurate. Our quality-control procedures are designed to assure that the information we compile and process is both accurate and complete. Coty endeavors to respond promptly to any questions about the accuracy of information from our consumers. 

**Security** 'Coty maintains security procedures designed to prevent unauthorized access to personally identifiable information. Coty uses a variety of multi-level security systems to control access to our sensitive information. All employees must have the appropriate access codes and be qualified to access such data. Coty conducts audits from time to time to maintain the integrity of customer data. Coty has physical security for our facilities and limited access to certain critical areas of the business. 

**Online Practices** 'Coty's online privacy practices apply to the collection and use of information collected online from individuals, prospects and customers who visit our website. These policies describe Coty's use of cookies and what choices individuals have over the use of information collected by such technologies. They can be found in our Online Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

**Coty's EU Safe Harbor Policy**  
Coty pledges to conduct its business according to the European Union (EU) Safe Harbor Principles and the Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ's) issued by the US Department of Commerce on July 21, 2000. 

**Notice-** Prior to the transfer of any non-public personal information from any EU Country to the US, Coty requires confirmation from the EU controller from whom Coty acquires any such information that the data subjects from whom the information was derived have been provided with proper Notice pursuant to the applicable EU Member State Data Protection law. 

**Choice** \- Prior to the transfer of any non-public personal information from the EU to the US, Coty requires contractual confirmation from the EU controller from whom Coty acquired the information that the data subjects from whom the information was derived have been provided with the Choice to determine how their information may be used pursuant to the applicable EU member State Data Protection law.  
In addition to choice regarding the use of information, Coty, upon request, will remove an individual's name and related information from its direct marketing solicitations.  
In order to have sufficient information to confirm the identity of an individual and have the necessary information to complete the opt-out request, Coty provides an opt-out form in the Beauty Pass area at [_http://www.cotyshop.com/_](http://www.cotyshop.com/) which the consumer can fill out, or by sending an e-mail to us at [_talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com).  
Written communication should be addresses as follows:  
Attn: E-Business Consumer Contact  
EU Safe Harbor Opt-Out  
Coty Beauty  
One Park Avenue 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
United States 

**Data Integrity** -Coty takes reasonable steps to assure the information which is transferred from the EU to the US is reliable, accurate and complete. The steps Coty takes to assure data integrity are made in light of the purposes for which the personal information is used. 

**Onward Transfer** \- Coty complies with the notice and choice principles as described above for all data which is disclosed or transferred to a third party. Coty may occasionally use agents to perform processing tasks on our behalf and under our instructions. Coty requires that its agents either: 

  * Subscribe to the EU Safe Harbor Principles, the EU Data Protection Directive or another adequacy finding; or
  * Enter into a written agreement with Coty requiring them to provide the same level of protection as Coty. 

**Security-** Coty has in place a security policy to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Coty has designated an individual to serve as its security officer. That person is responsible for conducting investigations into any alleged computer or network compromises, incidents or problems and ensuring the proper disciplinary action is taken against those who violate Coty's security policy.  
Any security compromises or potential security compromises and any inquiries concerning security should be reported to the Coty Consumer Advocate. Contact information is provided below. 

**Access** \- An individual may make a request to Coty for access to any personal information Coty maintains on that individual. The individual has the right to correct, amend, or delete that information when it is inaccurate. This right only applies to personal information relating to the individual making the request and is subject to other limitations as defined by law.  
Individuals who wish to make an access request should direct such a request to Coty's Consumer Advocate. This individual can be contacted by E-mail at: [_talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) or in writing at: Attn: E-Business Consumer Contact  
EU Safe Harbor Opt-Out  
Coty Beauty  
One Park Avenue 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
United States

**Enforcement** -Individuals who wish to file a complaint or who take issue with Coty's EU Safe Harbor policies should direct such communication to Coty's Consumer Advocate at the address described above. Currently, Coty is additionally seeking participation in third-party dispute resolution programs.  
Coty is also subject to the jurisdiction of the US Federal Trade Commission. Should an individual be unable to resolve a complaint, they may contact the Federal Trade Commission at the following address:  
Federal Trade Commission  
Attn: Consumer Response Center  
600 Pennsylvania Avenue NW  
Washington, DC 20580  
www.ftc.gov 

Back to Top

**Coty's Australian Privacy Policy**  
Coty supports the protection of consumers' privacy rights as a fundamental element of our business. We are committed to maintaining high standards of privacy and security in the way we conduct our business. Coty pledges to conduct its business according to the following principles.  
Coty recognizes that consumers have rights regarding the use and dissemination of information about themselves. Coty adheres to the National Privacy Principles. This ideology forms the basis of the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000, which controls the use of personal data. 

**Choice** 'Coty is careful to recognize any valid requests from individuals to suppress their names from our marketing efforts. Consumers may request to opt-out by going to the form in the Beauty Pass area at <http://www.cotyshop.com/> or by email at:  
[ _talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) or in writing at:  
Attn: E-Business Consumer Contact  
EU Safe Harbor Opt-Out  
Coty Beauty  
One Park Avenue 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
United States 

**Compliance** 'Coty is compliant with the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act of 2000 of Australia. Coty endeavors to operate within industry guidelines and privacy legislation in every country where we have a presence. Coty fully supports and conforms to the guidelines set down in the Australian Direct Marketing Association (ADMA) Code of Practice. Coty supports industry self-regulation and believes such actions are the best way to protect the privacy of the consumer. Coty maintains quality-control procedures aimed at assuring that our information is accurate. Our quality-control procedures are designed to assure the information we compile and process is both accurate and complete. Coty will respond within a reasonable time to any questions about the accuracy of information from our clients and the consumer. 

**Security** 'Coty maintains security procedures designed to ensure information will not be made available to any unauthorized persons or businesses. Coty uses a variety of multi-level security systems to control access to our sensitive information. Coty employees must have the appropriate access codes and be qualified to access specific data and applications. 

**Online Practices** 'Coty's online privacy practices apply to the collection and use of personal information collected online from individuals, prospects and customers who visit our website. These policies describe Coty's use of cookies and what choices individuals have over the use of personal information collected by such technologies and can be found in our Online Privacy Policy. For more information on Coty's information practices and privacy policy in Australia and New Zealand, please contact: 

This individual can be contacted by E-mail at:  
[ _talktous@cotyinc.com_](mailto:talktous@cotyinc.com) or in writing at:  
Attn: E-Business Consumer Contact  
EU Safe Harbor Opt-Out  
Coty Beauty  
One Park Avenue 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
United States
